<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Sport Shop</title>
	<atom:link href="https://https://marknrecaj.github.io/SportShop/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://https://marknrecaj.github.io/SportShop</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 19:40:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The DOs and DON&#8217;Ts of Buying Football Boots</title>
		<link>https://https://marknrecaj.github.io/SportShop/the-dos-and-donts-of-buying-football-boots/</link>
					<comments>https://https://marknrecaj.github.io/SportShop/the-dos-and-donts-of-buying-football-boots/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 19:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/sport-shop/?p=109</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[With the English Premier League in full swing, the craze for football remains to be as prominent as ever. Want to try out the moves you’ve seen your favourite footballers exhibit this season? You need the right boots for that! Here are the dos and don’ts of buying football boots. The DOs 1. Choosing the Right Boots [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>With the <a href="https://www.bbc.com/sport/football/premier-league">English Premier League</a> in full swing, the craze for football remains to be as prominent as ever. Want to try out the moves you’ve seen your favourite footballers exhibit this season? You need the right boots for that!</p>



<p>Here are the dos and don’ts of buying football boots.</p>



<h3>The DOs</h3>



<p><strong>1. Choosing the Right Boots for the Right Surface.</strong><br>When picking out football boots, it’s important that you keep in mind the surface you’ll be playing on. Different types of boots are designed for different purposes, and the last thing you want to do is choose ones that aren’t suitable for the pitch you’ll be playing on. Doing so can affect your performance and result in you being unable to adhere to the game style.<br><strong>2. Picking Shoes That Match Your Feet Shape</strong><br>You can’t toss around the ball effortlessly if the shoes you’re wearing don’t complement your feet shape! Do get that perfect fit, make sure the boots you pick out properly suit the shape of your feet. Sometimes the right football boot is different from the shoe size we usually wear because of the way it’s designed. Make sure that the ones you get perfectly align with both your feet, even if it means getting a size you haven’t previously bought.<br><strong>3. Picking Comfort Over Style</strong><br>No matter what type of shoes you’re getting, comfort is a must and that holds for football boots as well. After all, how will you be able to play the game if you’re not comfortable? When it comes to selecting footwear, comfort always trumps style!</p>



<h3>The DONT’S</h3>



<p><strong>1. Gambling on the Size</strong><br>Don’t make the mistake of buying a pair that’s just a little too big for you in the hopes that you’ll grow into it. Likewise, don’t buy a pair that’s a little too tight either with the expectations of it loosening up after you’ve played a few games. The trick is to get a size that fits you perfectly from the get-go. Just like you need to pick a pair that matches your feet shape, you also need the right size to be able to kick and run with them on easily.</p>



<p><strong>2. Buying a Pair of Boots Because of Celebrity Status</strong><br>Even if your favourite football player wears a certain brand of football boots or launched their own line of athletic footwear, don’t let that be the only reason you end up buying those shoes. It’s okay to want to imitate successful footballers, but that doesn’t mean you should buy a pair designed by <a href="https://www.buzz.ie/football/nike-new-ronaldinho-boots-258872">Ronaldinho</a> or recently worn by Messi despite them not being the right fit for you! Go for shoes you can actually comfortably wear and play in.<br><strong>3. Being Afraid to Buy Online</strong><br>Finally, don’t be afraid of buying football boots online! Not only is this more economical as you often get to avail special discounts and online deals, but it’s also more convenient. If you know your size for the particular type of boots you want, then simply order them online now, or visit your nearest sports store to try them out and then place your order online.<br>Avail the <strong>best football boots sale</strong> for 2020 online at Pro Direct Online! As a premium <strong>UK</strong>-based shoe store, we offer <strong>affordable football boots</strong> from the biggest brands. Shop Now at our online store!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://marknrecaj.github.io/SportShop/the-dos-and-donts-of-buying-football-boots/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 3 Best Football Boots</title>
		<link>https://https://marknrecaj.github.io/SportShop/the-3-best-football-boots/</link>
					<comments>https://https://marknrecaj.github.io/SportShop/the-3-best-football-boots/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 19:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/sport-shop/?p=105</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[No matter what position you play, you need to have a high-quality pair of football boots. For strikers, however, choosing the right footwear is even more important in order to score goals and be able to glide along the field seamlessly.Here are our top picks for football boots for strikers. Nike Mercurial Superfly 7 Elite [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>No matter what position you play, you need to have a high-quality pair of football boots. For strikers, however, choosing the right footwear is even more important in order to score goals and be able to glide along the field seamlessly.<br>Here are our top picks for football boots for strikers.</p>



<h3>Nike Mercurial Superfly 7 Elite</h3>



<p><br>The Nike Mercurial Superfly 7 Elite is definitely the talk of the town this season. As one of the most coveted football boot currently, it’s a huge hit amongst strikers as well as other forwards.</p>



<p>While the upgrades from the previous generation may not be immediately visible, once you try these on and test them out, you’ll notice the improvements. More flexible and much softer than the previous versions, these boots are a piece of art. Even more staggering is their strength and durability despite the thinness of the boots.<br>If you’re looking to up your game, Nike Mercurial Superfly 7 Elite is the perfect choice for you! Made using 360 technology, these boots are a striker’s best friend and will help you score many miraculous goals.</p>



<h3>PUMA Men’s Evo Speed Football Boots</h3>



<p>Puma Men’s Evo Speed Football Boots have been designed to optimize the wearer’s speed and agility and increase their traction. This makes them extremely suitable for strikers who need to move swiftly across the field during the game. Light on the feet, they’re made from premium leather. This makes them super comfortable to wear, while the blond outsole further helps with speed and stability.<br>What makes this boot design stand out is that it offers minimalistic heel counter with traction studs. Thus, it maximizes the player’s comfort and provides stability.</p>



<h3>Adidas X 19.1</h3>



<p>The laceless athletic footwear tradition continues with Adidas’s all-new Adidas X 19 collection. While the brand has been offering seed boots throughout their X collection, with the X 19.1, you’re in for some cool new updates. Designed specifically for strikers, the boots help maintain a fast pace and smooth agility, facilitating and even improving overall performance.<br>These boots are made from Adidas’s unique “X-Layskin” material. This gives them their distinct glove-like fitting quality, making them even more suitable for strikers. The new 19.1 upgrade is, in fact, Adidas’s fastest boot to have been released and is especially beneficial for footballers playing off the shoulder.<br>Available in multiple colours, you definitely don’t want to miss out on these! After all, Mo Salah wears these too.<br><a href="https://www.prodirectonline.com/">Pro Direct Online</a>&nbsp;has the&nbsp;<strong>best football boots for sale</strong>! As a&nbsp;<strong>UK</strong>-based sports shoe store, we offer&nbsp;<strong>affordable football boots</strong>&nbsp;from the biggest brands at amazing discounts.&nbsp;<a href="https://www.prodirectonline.com/adidas/x-19.html">Shop now</a>&nbsp;at our online store!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://marknrecaj.github.io/SportShop/the-3-best-football-boots/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
